<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist>
  <schema id="org.gnome.shell.extensions.username-avatar"
          path="/org/gnome/shell/extensions/username-avatar/">
    <key name="show-hostname" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Show computer name in the panel label</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, the panel label appends the local hostname after the account name.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="show-username" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Show username in the panel label</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, the top bar shows the account name next to the avatar and optional hostname.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="show-avatar" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Show avatar in the top bar</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, the top bar shows the user avatar before the account name.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="keep-awake" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Keep the session awake</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, the extension inhibits session idle so the screen saver does not activate.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="place-after-navigation" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Place after Apps and Places</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, the panel item is placed after the Apps and Places menus if they are loaded.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="show-topbar" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Show the extension in the top bar</summary>
      <description>
        When disabled, the quick settings menu entry remains available but the panel item is hidden.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="show-quick-settings" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Show the extension in the quick settings menu</summary>
      <description>
        When disabled, the right-side quick settings toggle is hidden.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="quick-settings-toggle-topbar-only" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Quick settings click toggles only the top bar item</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, clicking the username tile in quick settings only shows or hides the top bar item. When disabled, clicking the tile disables the whole extension instead.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="hide-topbar-fullscreen" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Hide the top bar while an app is fullscreen</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, the GNOME top bar is hidden whenever the focused window is fullscreen.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="hide-topbar-fullscreen-all-monitors" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Apply fullscreen autohide on all monitors</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, a focused fullscreen window on any monitor can hide the GNOME top bar. When disabled, fullscreen autohide only applies to the primary monitor.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="hide-topbar-maximized" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Hide the top bar while the focused app is maximized</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, the GNOME top bar is hidden whenever the focused window is maximized.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="hide-topbar-touching" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Hide the top bar while the focused app touches the top edge</summary>
      <description>
        When enabled, the GNOME top bar is hidden whenever the focused window reaches the top edge of the screen.
      </description>
    </key>
  </schema>
</schemalist>
